see now I try to be cool for a video for
once and you know I try that I had a
fashion scape the first time ever and I
under pain like look at that 145 K is it
worth it I don't know [__]
oh god please not more Oh God and now
I'm out here about to spend a thousand
points to get this Slayer how I'm like
look at me I'm just such a savage oh my
god alright let's just get it over with
yep alright there we go
now I think we're good for the intro
alright hello everyone how you guys
doing hope you guys are having a
wonderful day today we're here with
another video in today's video will be
not me well I will be doing the money
making method however it'll be more me
showing you guys how I made literal bank
in old school runescape so basically
this is by far my favorite money making
method in the game it's the one that's
made me the most money in the game it's
literally the best GP per time invested
by far out of anything I know in the
game now the problem is I don't do it as
much anymore because there's less and
less margins but I have done it recently
and you can get good ones the problem is
is I find a lot of people like to
undercut and I don't have the time
anymore when I work in the hardcore
Ironman I just want to chill on this
account I don't want to be heavy
invested into something but we are going
to go and show you guys today how I made
probably yeah at least 10 mil a day
during the summer over last summer and
even up until now you can still I mean
if you do it right and you're paying
attention you can get 10 mil a day
pretty uh pretty easily after this video
it'll be hard and trust me I understand
that I mean with as many people that are
going to watch this it's not going to be
profitable this is why I never released
this video because I knew the minute I
did it I was going to kill the item for
a while now this did actually get out at
one point I did actually release a video
where my secret item was released and
yeah so anyone that found out about then
congratulations to you you were the
first my video you earned it you earned
it but today we're gonna talk so let's
go ahead I'll go to the grand exchange
and we'll show you what you got to do so
I did have a lot of money when doing
this believe me if I'm making 10 mil a
day I was making a lot of money this is
how I hit a bill last summer but now the
methods kind of dead and I mean if I
check it right now there's like a 400 K
margin I'm probably just gonna end the
video
go do it myself but if we buy a Ferro
scepter three four
you know however much of buys for five
point two mil and then we go ahead and
buy a Ferro scepter uncharged I mean
there's multiple ways to go about this
if you don't want to lose the money by
buying and selling this one you could
actually just uncharged this and sell it
and that'll totally not I mean that'll
tell you the same thing but as you guys
can see I instant bought the last one
for 507 3k and I sold her for 506 -
there's not that many of these sold and
bought an hour maybe eight to ten
depending on which one you're doing the
charged ones are bought and sold more
than the uncharged ones but you need the
uncharged ones to ultimately charge them
so either way you're gonna have to buy
these now if there's only a 10k
difference between the insta buy and
they slow by just in some biome I mean
whoever is doing it I'm more than
willing to buy four of them okay we got
one we got one that's fine I'll grab a
couple more for the for the sell price
and I'll show you guys basically what I
would do even right now there's a really
good margin on it so it's kind of proof
that it works but those will take like
maybe 15 minutes to buy but as you guys
can see there is a hundred and thirty k
margin just off of charging them and
I'll show you how easy it is to actually
charge these it's ridiculous like I
they're the only reason that this has a
big margin is because not a lot of
people know about this item it's a
really weird item it's expensive it by
slow and it's kind of you know these
used to be eight mil and back then there
was bigger margins but now they're down
to five so they're maybe a little less I
got a comment on my last money-making
video asking me how I actually found the
money making method and I thought that
that was a really strange thing but I
think it's kind of vital um you find
them in the weirdest Wade's and here we
are on YouTube shout out to a Third Age
film aka soup aka the best quest guides
an old school runescape but if we look
here he has a video from about a year
ago yeah May 14th it's a little while
ago that's when I got this method so it
makes sense why I did it over the summer
but I actually just found it through his
video I don't even think he intended to
actually find something this good and
the reason he didn't actually expose it
is cuz he did something very very wrong
but we'll go ahead and look through it
right now basically this video he goes
over and talks about achievement diary
money making methods one one meal plus
per hour whatever but basically one of
the things in the Diaries is that you
can actually charge Pharaoh scepters
two six charges or maybe five instead of
three now this added perk of the Diary
really does nothing in regards to you
know it actually makes it slower to make
money because you have to take the
charges off to be able to sell them back
but this was kind of a cool thing that I
learned basically the reason he didn't
make any money is as you can see here he
goes ahead and install of these scepters
and that's the first problem you don't
want to answer by scepter so you don't
want to sell them if you instant buy and
sell you probably won't make much money
at all I'm sure he just got a good time
with a good margin and he did here but
if you actually slow buy and then slow
sell you make a ton of money and that's
what I'm gonna be doing today when mind
by now while making 10 mil a day may
seem a little bit unreasonable as for
the prices now it's not really that hard
to do personally I had two to three
hundred mill pretty much at all times in
cash and I was able to always keep those
in fare acceptors and at the time we got
one to buy at the time they also had
three to four hundred K margins and for
the most part I almost always was
merging Farrow scepters while they were
on the rise after the house portal
update so for the most part I was
constantly either making money through
just being able to charge the fare
receptors or through them just going up
and priced you to the Poh so either one
I was making hella cash and there we go
took me not even probably ten minutes to
buy the three so I mean I guess at that
rate you could assume you could buy
about eighteen per hour but you know I
mean obviously it all depends on how
many people are buying and selling right
now now with that said I'm gonna blink
my dragon claws but we do have four and
that's pretty much the inventory you're
going to want to run with your go
I mean every inventory you need you're
going to want to wear a Ferro scepter
now this isn't necessary however it is
really nice for the teleport puts you
right next to the guy that charges it if
you have the money for it which you will
if you're doing this method I recommend
getting it on top of that you need six
gold seals or six gold artifacts in
general to be able to charge these
scepters so for this inventory I'm going
to have to take 24 so let's go ahead and
buy those they're typically pretty cheap
maybe after this video they hit a
relative high they aren't all that in
stock because they are such a strange
item not a lot of people bank stuff
after doing pyramid plunder but for
those that do they actually make a
little bit of money off of these so as
you guys can see we take that now we
have a full inventory basically the
setup I'd
is just go ahead use your Ferro sceptre
and then a teleport method to wherever
you want to go personally I go to castle
wars but I mean word wherever you feel
fit basically from there once you have
that your inventory set up just go to
the first teleport and you will be next
to a guardian mummy
talk to him real quick and it's pretty
simple just press spacebar and then one
and then spacebar and then one now the
average trip for me takes about 20 to 30
seconds and you make a ton of money so
as you can see they're discharging right
here each charge really takes like 5k
coins to charge and you're making 130 K
per one now right there I made 130 K per
one and that took me about twenty or
thirty seconds that's I mean it's 520 K
it's a really good money making method
it's one that I've kept in my back
pocket for a while now and just because
I don't use it anymore I really just
figured it was a time to you know let it
be free so hopefully you guys take
advantage of this I mean I'm gonna go
and show you guys how much money we made
obviously but there's so much money to
be made here and this video is probably
gonna ruin it I know my videos typically
ruin some methods not all I think it's
very specific like stuff like gothics
restores I ruined because I mean you
know there's not a lot of people that
need gothics restores just as there's
not a lot of people that need these like
they're not constantly bought and sold
that's why it's a really hard money
making method to release people always
used to get mad at me because I never
released my best money making method
that's because it was just so hard to do
so I guess if we go ahead and add up
here you guys see that twenty point I
guess 20 mil and 250 K is about what I
bought them all for and once you assume
that I can sell them for five one and
nine eight each I guess we'll go do that
you see that I turned 20 mil 250 K to 20
ml in pretty much 800 K so I made 550 K
in a matter of 20 or 30 seconds and it
only took me 10 minutes to buy the
supplies literally just the best money
making method in the game and I'm just
gonna go ruin it so hopefully you guys
enjoy the video if you guys did make
sure to leave a like I know it's a
pretty savage money making method
I almost said that I'm giving it away
it's it's a special place in my heart
but for the most part I'm investing into
stuff now so I really doesn't matter to
me hopefully you guys make use of it
while you can and for those that aren't
able to make money on it because they
got here a little late make sure you
subscribe to my channel so you get there
as soon as you can in the future but
to be honest it'll be back up and
running probably in a month or two once
everyone loses money on it because the
way that these things work and I guess I
was gonna end the video but I'll talk
about it real quick why I think these
have such a big margin is because
they're really unstable as far as price
they're worth five mil to 5.2 ml and the
only real use for it other than
teleports I mean they used to hold a
price of one to two ml before they got
put into P OHS so really the only thing
that makes these things fluctuate is a
Poh how much or how many people actually
need them for that and because of that
it's pretty easy for these to sway
between you know a 100 200 K price
within a day and if that price ends up
going down then you may lose your margin
and that's why I think eventually this
money making method will probably come
back so hopefully you guys enjoyed if
you guys did make sure to leave a like
obviously subscribe to this channel if
you enjoy the content comment down below
anything you guys want to see in the
future or comment about how I ruined
your money making method and your upset
about it either one
check out my clan chat in-game large exp
lamp twitter and twitch in the
description down below along with a
discord but with that said hopefully you
guys have a wonderful day and peace by
the way figure just one without saying